maianscriptworld.co.uk 2018-08-16

# Privacy Policy: MSWorld - Maian Script World - Free Responsive PHP Software for Personal or Business Use - PHP / MySQL / HTML5

This policy covers how I use your personal information. I take your privacy seriously and will take all measures to protect your personal information. Maian Script World tries to fully comply with the [GDPR](https://ico.org.uk/) law that came into affect on May 25th 2018.

**ADDRESS / CONTACT INFORMATION**

Any address or contact information received will only be used to fulfill your order and is used solely for internal record/book keeping. This enables you to obtain receipts for your purchases and me to keep book keeping, which are required by law.

**EMAIL ADDRESS**

Your email is used to let you know of related products, product coupons and product updates related to your purchased product. I will never sell or redistribute your information to third parties or promotional companies. To subscribe you can either give your express consent via the newsletter signup page or when you purchase a product. If you DO NOT give your consent, you will receive no emails.

You can unsubscribe at any time via a promotional email.

**EXTERNAL WEBSITE LINKS**

My website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave my site, you should note that I do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, I cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**COOKIES**

The [forum](https://www.maianscriptworld.co.uk/forums/) will set a cookie if you elect to remain logged in. You have the option of setting this on login. The forum cookie is harmless and contains NO user identifying information. Some of the Maian Script World sites may also utilise the [AddThis](http://www.addthis.com/privacy) platform for social sharing.

**ANALYTICS**

This website and all commercial websites use the [Open Web Analytics](http://www.openwebanalytics.com/) system. This helps to track what pages people are visiting and what platforms they are using for promotion and marketing. No user indentifiable data is recorded. More information on the [OWA website](http://www.openwebanalytics.com/).

**SSL**

This website is protected by a secure socket layer to encrypt data before it is transmitted across the web. Look for the padlock in your address bar for more info. Any data you send on the Maian Script World website or product websites is encrypted during transmission.

Any questions, please [contact me](https://www.maianscriptworld.co.uk/contact).
